Everyone deserves a second shot.
Thunderbolts* is a action, science fiction,
adventure film directed by Jake Schreier.
After finding themselves ensnared in a death trap, seven disillusioned castoffs must embark on a
dangerous mission that will force them to confront the darkest corners of their pasts.
Yelena Belova, played by Florence Pugh.
Bucky Barnes, played by Sebastian Stan.
Valentina Allegra de Fontaine, played by Julia Louis-Dreyfus.
Robert Reynolds, played by Lewis Pullman.
Alexei Shostakov, played by David Harbour.
John Walker, played by Wyatt Russell.
Thunderbolts*  is a 2025 American superhero film based on
Marvel Comics featuring the team Thunderbolts.
Produced by Marvel Studios and distributed by Walt Disney Studios Motion
Pictures, it is the 36th film in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU).
The film was directed by Jake Schreier from a screenplay by Eric Pearson and Joanna Calo, and stars an ensemble cast featuring Florence Pugh, Sebastian Stan, Wyatt
Russell, Olga Kurylenko, Lewis Pullman, Geraldine Viswanathan, Chris Bauer, Wendell Pierce, David Harbour, Hannah John-Kamen, and Julia Louis-Dreyfus.
In the film, a group of antiheroes are caught in a deadly trap and
forced to work together on a dangerous mission.
Marvel Studios first teased the formation of an MCU Thunderbolts team in 2021.
The film was revealed to be in development in June 2022,
when Schreier and Pearson were attached.
The main cast was revealed in September, with
additional casting through early 2023.
Lee Sung Jin joined to rewrite the script by March 2023, one of several creatives who
returned to work with Schreier from the Netflix series Beef (2023–present).
Production was delayed by the 2023 Hollywood labor
disputes, causing some cast changes in early 2024.
Calo joined by then for further rewrites.
Filming took place from February to June 2024 at Trilith Studios and Atlanta Metro
Studios in Atlanta, Georgia, and on location in Utah and Kuala Lumpur.
Thunderbolts* premiered on April 22, 2025, at the Cineworld Leicester Square in London, England, and
was released in the United States on May 2 as the final film of Phase Five of the MCU.
The asterisk in the title was the subject of commentary during the film's marketing campaign, and was explained by the reveal at the end of the film that the
Thunderbolts team is rebranded as the "New Avengers"; the title is changed to The New Avengers during the film's end credits and in some post-release marketing.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics, but
underperformed at the box office, grossing $382 million.
The film explores themes of new york city, superhero,
villain, based on comic, super power.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.